const data = [
  {
    question: "A connective tissue",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Has no matrix", "Covers the skin", "None of these"],
    correctAnswer: "Has abundant matrix",
  },

  {
    question:
      "Which one of the following contains the largest quantity of extracellular material?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Striated muscle",
      "Myelinated nerve fibres",
      "Stratified epithelium",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Areolar tissue",
  },
  {
    question: "Primary function of subdermal fat in the skin of mammals is",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "To preserve collected sum",
      "To prevent the jerks",
      "To protect the body",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To act as a heat proof  matter",
  },
  {
    question: "When collagen fibres are removed from the areolar tissue",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Tissue becomes hard",
      "Tissue becomes hard and inelastic",
      "Remains unchanged",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Tissue becomes loose and elastic",
  },
  {
    question: "The types of fibres found in connective tissues are",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Collagan fibres", "Elastic fibres", "Reticular fibres"],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Whale is a warm-blooded animal which lives in cold sea. Which organ of its body makes it hot",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Pelage", "Muscles", "Blood vessels"],
    correctAnswer: "Blubber",
  },
  {
    question: "Which one of the following is not a fibrillar protein?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Elastin", "Collagen", "Myosin"],
    correctAnswer: "Albumin",
  },
  {
    question: "The giant cell is formed by the fusion of",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Plasma cell", "Mast cell", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "Macrophage",
  },
  {
    question: "The areolar tissue connects",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Two bones",
      "Muscle and the bone",
      "Muscle and the fat tissue",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Muscles and their compound",
  },
  {
    question: "Name the tissue which has loose arrangement of cells",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Epithelial tissues",
      "Muscles tissues",
      "Nerve tissues",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Connective tissues",
  },
  {
    question: "What is/are the main functions of connective tissue?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Bind other tissues",
      "Support other tissues",
      "Protects other tissues",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Both A and B",
  },
  {
    question: "The major types of connective tissues are",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Adipose tissue",
      "Fibrous Tissue",
      "Cartilage, bone, and blood",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "Which makes the loose connective tissue elastic",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Tendons", "Ligaments", "Cartilage"],
    correctAnswer: "Collagens",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The strong and flexible fibers of collagens are found in which type of connective tissue?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Fibrous connective tissue",
      "Adipose tissue",
      "Cartilage",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Loose connective tissue",
  },
  {
    question: "The functions of loose connective tissue include:",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Bind epithelia to underlying tissues",
      "As packing material to hold organ",
      "Connect bones to bones",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Both A and B",
  },
  {
    question: "Why fibrous connective tissues create very strong cords?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "They lie parallel to one another",
      "They connect muscles to bones or to other muscles",
      "They connect bones to bones",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "Which fibrous connective tissue connect bones to bones?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Tendons", "Cartilage", "Bone"],
    correctAnswer: "Ligaments",
  },
  {
    question: "The type of loose connective tissue that store lipid is",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Cartilage", "Bone", "Blood"],
    correctAnswer: "Adipose tissue",
  },
  {
    question: "Cartilage are present in the ________ ear.",
    incorrectAnswers: ["middle", "inner", "none"],
    correctAnswer: "outer",
  },
  {
    question: "Find the correct statement",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Tendon is a specialized connective tissue",
      "Cartilage is a loose connective tissue",
      "Adipose tissue is a dense connective tissue",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Areolar tissue is a loose connective tissue",
  },
  {
    question: "Tip of the nose and external ears have",
    incorrectAnswers: ["areolar tissue", "ligament", "bone"],
    correctAnswer: "cartilage",
  },
  {
    question: "Mast cells contain",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "heparin and calcitonin",
      "seratonin and melanin",
      "vasopressin and relaxin",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "heparin and histamine",
  },
  {
    question: "Antibodies are secreted by",
    incorrectAnswers: ["adipose cells", "reticular cells", "mast cells"],
    correctAnswer: "plasma cells",
  },
  {
    question: "The structures of cells in the connective tissues is",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "squamous matrix",
      "ciliated matrix",
      "stratified matrix",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "extracellular matrix",
  },
  {
    question: "The tissue which binds and suppors other tissues is called",
    incorrectAnswers: ["linkage tissue", "muscle tissue", "nervous tissue"],
    correctAnswer: "connective tissue",
  },
  {
    question: "The functions of the connective tissues, included",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "provision of structural support",
      "fat storage",
      "act as a medium of gaseous exchange",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The yellow pigment that is present in the stratum Corneum is known as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["melanin", "hemoglobin", "oxyhemoglobin"],
    correctAnswer: "carotenes",
  },
  {
    question: "The rod-like structure that joins bone to bone is named as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["tendons", "cartilage", "aponeuroses"],
    correctAnswer: "ligaments",
  },
  {
    question: "The fat cells are normally called as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["chondrocytes", "osteocytes", "none of above"],
    correctAnswer: "adipocytes",
  },
  {
    question: "The cross-sectional appearance of the fibroblasts is",
    incorrectAnswers: ["butterfly like", "pea like", "pear like"],
    correctAnswer: "star like",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Leptin acts on the hpyothalamus, decreases the appetite, ultimately resulting in",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "weight gain",
      "maintain sugar in body",
      "maintain calcium in the body",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "weight loss",
  },
  {
    question: "The diameter of the reticular fibers is about",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "0.4-6 micrometer",
      "0.7-5 micrometer",
      "0.8-10 micrometer",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "0.5-2 micrometer",
  },
  {
    question: "The dense connective tissues are",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "less flexible",
      "resistant to stress",
      "less amount of amorphous ground substance",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question: "A large aggregate of adipocytes is termed as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["aggregation", "clump", "oils"],
    correctAnswer: "adipose tissues",
  },
  {
    question: "The reticular fibers are made up of",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "type i collagen",
      "type ii collagen",
      "type iv collagen",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "type iii collagen",
  },
  {
    question: "The function of the adipocytes embodied with",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "secreting elastin",
      "secreting glycosaminoglycan",
      "maintaining calcium in the body",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "lipid storage",
  },
  {
    question: "The functions of the connective tissues, included",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "provision of structural support",
      "fat storage",
      "act as a medium of gaseous exchange",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The motile phagocytic cells, found in the connective tissues throughout the body, called as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["macrophage", "Histiocytes", "migrant cells"],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question: "The diameter of the masts cells is about",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "10-20 micrometer",
      "50-70 micrometer",
      "30-50 micrometer",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "20-30 micrometer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The supporting framework of the loose connective tissues is called",
    incorrectAnswers: ["mesentery", "Omentum", "superficial layer"],
    correctAnswer: "stoma",
  },
  {
    question: "The tendons entirely composed of",
    incorrectAnswers: ["dissolved form", "salts", "water content"],
    correctAnswer: "collagen fibers",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The antibodies belonging to the immunoglobulin E variety are secreted by the",
    incorrectAnswers: ["mast cells", "fixed cells", "none of above"],
    correctAnswer: "plasma cells",
  },
  {
    question: "The identified varieties of the collagens are about",
    incorrectAnswers: ["10", "30", "40"],
    correctAnswer: "20",
  },
  {
    question: "The diameter of the elastic fibers is about",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "0.2-2 micrometer",
      "0.2-4 micrometer",
      "0.2-6 micrometer",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "0.2-1 micrometer",
  },
  {
    question: "The diamter of the white adipose tissues is nearly",
    incorrectAnswers: ["10 micrometer", "40 micrometer", "50-100 micrometer"],
    correctAnswer: "50-150 micrometer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The cells that synthesized and remain in the connective tissues are termed as",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "resident cells only",
      "fixed cells only",
      "migrant cells",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "resident and fixed cells",
  },
  {
    question: "In adipocytes, the fats are stored as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["oil", "carbs", "proteins"],
    correctAnswer: "triglycerides",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The cells that enter the connective tissues via bloodstreams are named as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["resident cells", "fixed cells", "mesenchymal cells"],
    correctAnswer: "migrant cells",
  },
  {
    question: "Dense collective tissues, may be having",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "regular connective tissues only",
      "irregular connective tissues only",
      "compact tissues",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "regular and irregular connective tissues",
  },
  {
    question: "The migrant cells, incorporated with",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "mast cell and macrophages",
      "plasma cells",
      "leukocytes",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ground substance of the loose connective tissues is dissolved in",
    incorrectAnswers: ["alcohol only", "xylene only", "melanocytes"],
    correctAnswer: "alcohol and xylene",
  },
  {
    question: "The connective tissues are",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "packing material of the body",
      "anchoring material of the body",
      "embedding material for many structures",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The cord-like structure that attaches muscles to the bones is called",
    incorrectAnswers: ["ligament", "cartilage", "aponeuroses"],
    correctAnswer: "tendons",
  },
  {
    question: "Resident cells, included",
    incorrectAnswers: ["fibroblasts", "adipocytes", "mesenchymal stem cells"],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question: "The diameter of the plasma cells is about",
    incorrectAnswers: ["10 micrometer", "30 micrometer", "60 micrometer"],
    correctAnswer: "20 micrometer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Leukocytes are migrant cells in the connective tissues which includes",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "neutrophils",
      "eosinophil",
      "lymphocytes and monocytes",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question: "The functions of the fibroblast, embodied with",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "secreting collagen",
      "secreting elastin",
      "secreting glycosaminoglycan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question: "The functions of the fibroblast, embodied with",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "secreting collagen",
      "secreting elastin",
      "secreting glycosaminoglycan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A flattened and broad structure that joins sheet-like muscles to the bone is termed as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["ligaments", "cartilage", "tendon"],
    correctAnswer: "aponeuroses",
  },
  {
    question: "The mesenchymal cells appeared as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["butterfly like", "pea like", "pear like"],
    correctAnswer: "star like",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The color of the white adipose tissues is due to the pigment named as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["xanthophyll", "hemoglobin", "pepsin"],
    correctAnswer: "carotenoids",
  },
  {
    question: "The ground substance of the loose connective tissue is",
    incorrectAnswers: ["solid-like", "granule-like", "button-like"],
    correctAnswer: "fluid-like",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The mucous tissues contain the principal component of the umblical cord, called as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["fruit jelly", "Rofan jelly", "cutis"],
    correctAnswer: "Wharton jelly",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The mucous tissues contain the principal component of the umblical cord, called as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["fruit jelly", "Rofan jelly", "cutis"],
    correctAnswer: "Wharton jelly",
  },
  {
    question: "The polypeptide chains in the collagen fibers are",
    incorrectAnswers: ["beta chains", "gamma chains", "none of above"],
    correctAnswer: "alpha chains",
  },
  {
    question: "The mesenchymal connective tissues are present in the",
    incorrectAnswers: ["adults", "child", "old age"],
    correctAnswer: "developing embryo",
  },
  {
    question: "The collagen fibers composed of",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "1 polypeptide chain",
      "2 polypeptide chain",
      "lacks polypeptide",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "3 polypeptide chains",
  },
  {
    question: "The reticular connective tissues composed of",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "reticular cells",
      "reticular fibers",
      "type iii collagen",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question: "The diameter of the collagen fibers is about",
    incorrectAnswers: ["1-3 micrometer", "5-8 micrometer", "2-5 micrometer"],
    correctAnswer: "2-10 micrometer",
  },
  {
    question: "Oxygen reaches to the loose connective tissue via",
    incorrectAnswers: ["diffusion", "dissolved form", "veins"],
    correctAnswer: "capillaries",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The basic component of the loose connective tissue, incorporated in",
    incorrectAnswers: ["cells", "fibers", "ground substances"],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The basic component of the loose connective tissue, incorporated in",
    incorrectAnswers: ["cells", "fibers", "ground substances"],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question: "The hormone released by the white adipose tissue is termed as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["renin", "angiotensin", "kinase"],
    correctAnswer: "leptin",
  },
];

export default data;
